<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Marteal Cycle Works</title>
    <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Marteal Cycle Works</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:3000/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Still Trying to get this? WTF</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/still-trying-to-get-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/still-trying-to-get-this/</guid>
      <description>How does this work? The Transformative Humanities project asks Cornell faculty to talk about their own life-changing encounters with great works in the arts and humanities and how these works have transformed their scholarship and their lives. Here are their contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>updating my Fresh post in Forestry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/fresh-post-in-forestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/fresh-post-in-forestry/</guid>
      <description>Does this work? Marteal Cycleworks is founded on the belief that everyone deserves to experience joy, adventure, and wonder on a bike, and that every cyclist, whether an avid racer, an occasional tourer, or a total beginner deserves to be valued and respected as a person, a cyclist and a customer.
MCW was founded by Bob Marteal after years of avid cycling and shopping the available market looking for good customer service and a bicycle that felt right, but always winding up like so many others; frustrated and feeling there was no place for him in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My-First-Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description> yohohoho this is the posty post Hi, I am the Hugo Boilerplate. I hope you are enjoying this guide!
 how does this work ?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Hugo!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/example/</guid>
      <description>You’ll find this post in your content/posts directory.
To add new posts, simply add a file in the content/posts directory that follows the convention name-of-post.ext and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.
Hugo also offers powerful support for code snippets:
package main import &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; func print_hi(name string) { fmt.Println(&amp;#34;Hi, &amp;#34;, name) } func main() { print_hi(&amp;#34;Tom&amp;#34;) } //=&amp;gt; prints &amp;#39;Hi, Tom&amp;#39; to STDOUT.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>